{
    "id": "8361cbfdd03f4747a737e2324aee27c3",
    "title": "General Grammar Quiz (Gap Filling)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I often ……………………….. horror movies.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about habits, routines etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "am watching",
                "watch",
                "watches"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "855cfb8e7d8d4d0081bffda852c79723"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… tomorrow.",
            "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about pre-planned future events. ",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "am leaving",
                "will leave"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5dd6c647843648cbb130ad73656b4cb3"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………………. in May.",
            "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about pre-planned future events. ",
            "answers": [
                "marry",
                "will marry",
                "will get married",
                "are getting married"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "f1783bdc12f74e779544b5ab803fa530"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………. care of stray dogs and cats.",
            "description": "Use the simple present if this is a habit. The present continuous is used to talk about something that we are doing at the moment. ",
            "answers": [
                "takes",
                "take",
                "is taking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e286763781514e8d9384631fa76a903a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. run when I was just one year old.",
            "description": "Use could to talk about past ability. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "could able to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "200f790620914752a0ac041887b10a55"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. me you weren’t coming.",
            "description": "Both expressions can be used to criticize people for not doing things. ",
            "answers": [
                "could tell",
                "could have told",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e2ce1598a0eb4857bffda1f168e191f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "There ……………………….. be a bakery in that corner.",
            "description": "Use used to to talk about past habits and states.",
            "answers": [
                "was used to",
                "would",
                "used to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4e898c3f9597400c9317f55a420754b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… talk about her illnesses for hours.",
            "description": "Either would or used to can be used to talk about past habits. ",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "77b3c275bb854d358602f83decf36ef2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. working so hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "am not used to",
                "am not using to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e8dd01705a784693ad5649b66da0005d"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Where is Samuel?’ ‘He ……………………… to Russia.’",
            "description": "Has been is used to talk about finished visits. We use the present perfect to express ideas like these because he is still in Russia. ",
            "answers": [
                "has been",
                "has gone",
                "went"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0d1e689f32f84f7eb11350ec420dd337"
        },
        {
            "question": "We saw children ……………………….. in the park.",
            "description": "After see, we can use an ing form or an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "to play",
                "playing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3663cceac2c74add9d6c27fd23b319f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "You never let me ………………………… a sentence.",
            "description": "Finish is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "to finish",
                "finish",
                "finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c4727a8cb214e7f9fa235d04272c301"
        }
    ]
}